<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sierra Leone &#8211; MAKE Productions</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.makeproductions.com/tag/sierra-leone/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.makeproductions.com</link>
	<description>London and Singapore Media Production</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 13:22:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.7.11</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Sierra Leone Report IV</title>
		<link>http://www.makeproductions.com/sierra-leone-report-iv/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 15:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[makeproductions]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ebola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ebola outbreak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medecins Sans Frontiers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sierra Leone]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.harrytrussell.com/?p=2979</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com/sierra-leone-report-iv/">Sierra Leone Report IV</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com">MAKE Productions</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<section  class="content-section full-width with-col cover rella-no-padding rella-no-margin    content-section-5b6ad4fc391cb"><div class="row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column col-md-12"><div class="section-text text-block " ><p><strong>Director Jeremy Bristow reports from Bombeh, Sierra Leone, where he is filming the Ebola outbreak on behalf of Make Productions.</strong></p>
<p>Returned to 34 Bombeh road today.</p>
<p>Filmed sprayers getting into body suits. Chlorine mix being made and put into spray tanks. They started to spray the ground around the house.  The quarantine family watched from the veranda as sprayers spray steps and posts and move inside.</p>
<p>A large crowd is gathered round from all sides of the house.  Médecins Sans Frontiers addresses people and the crowd.  This is serious – stand back.</p>
<p>One of the Ebola suspects, a man of around 50 walks and sits in the back of the ambulance.  From a safe distance the medics start ask him questions and fill in notes.  The rest of the family look on. Sprayers are walking past.</p>
<p>Then he gets into the ambulance.</p>
<p>Then a man walks out holding a tiny two year-old.  They sit on the veranda and are asked questions.  They then climb in to ambulance.  The psycho-social counsellor the addresses ambulance driver. One of these men is very sick ‘please, please’ drive very slow.</p>
<p>Ambulance drives off into distance.</p>
<p>At the hospital</p>
<p>Filmed ambulance sitting waiting at hospital, one door open – just one foot poignantly sticks out.</p>
<p>Eventually two bio-dressed people in full protective clothing outfits get out and walk up to them.  50 year old gets out and walks down path towards the Isolation Centre. Man in Bio-body suit takes the little girl by her hand.  She looks up to him as they walk.</p>
<p>One of the earlier children, a girl, sits out on a plastic seat.  Later joined by a boy – from another family.</p>
<p>Inside the unit is dark.  People in bio-suits sweeping and mopping etc.</p>
<p>Another ambulance arrives with a young teenage girl and a 5 year-old boy get out and are walked to the isolation ward.</p>
<p>Cold blooded Dan averages around 36.0.</p>
<p>Me, I vary between 36.5 and 36.9 using the ear thermometer.   This morning I took three reading is 5 minutes. 36.7/36.9/36.8.<br />
I think normal is meant to be 37.3.</p>
<p>More later</p>
</div></div></div></section>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com/sierra-leone-report-iv/">Sierra Leone Report IV</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com">MAKE Productions</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sierra Leone Report II</title>
		<link>http://www.makeproductions.com/sierra-leone-report-ii/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2014 09:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[makeproductions]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ebola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ebola outbreak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medecins Sans Frontiers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sierra Leone]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://rhythmwp.staging.wpengine.com/?p=2440</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com/sierra-leone-report-ii/">Sierra Leone Report II</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com">MAKE Productions</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<section  class="content-section full-width with-col cover rella-no-padding rella-no-margin    content-section-5b6ad4fc4d1b8"><div class="row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column col-md-12"><div class="section-text text-block " ><p><strong>Director Jeremy Bristow’s third in a series of groundbreaking reports from Sierra Leone, where he is filming the Ebola outbreak on behalf of Make Productions.</strong></p>
<p>Our new fixer is briefing us on the local situation.  Ebola in Bo is comparatively low.  Local people are fearful of Médecins Sans Frontiers because they have come to believe few people come out alive.  They prefer to go to Freetown.</p>
<p>We weren’t able to film in the Médecins Sans Frontiers vehicle for the journey.  I gave them the 5D to film a nurse looking out of the window.   It was not a great success. Much of the time they are singing about going ‘on holiday’ and clowning around. The vehicle they were in has returned to Freetown.  Am not sure there is a similar vehicle Bo. Hope so.</p>
<p>The cameraman has got some wonderful thundercloud footage this evening.  Apparently, there are electric storms every night.  Am hoping we can get some thunder and lighten over the Médecins Sans Frontiers tented city!!!!!</p>
<p>Jeremy</p>
</div></div></div></section>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com/sierra-leone-report-ii/">Sierra Leone Report II</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com">MAKE Productions</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sierra Leone Report I</title>
		<link>http://www.makeproductions.com/director-jeremy-bristows-second-report-from-sierra-leone-where-he-is-filming-the-ebola-outbreak-on-behalf-of-make-productions/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 09:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[makeproductions]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ebola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ebola outbreak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medecins Sans Frontiers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sierra Leone]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://rhythmwp.staging.wpengine.com/?p=2439</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com/director-jeremy-bristows-second-report-from-sierra-leone-where-he-is-filming-the-ebola-outbreak-on-behalf-of-make-productions/">Sierra Leone Report I</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com">MAKE Productions</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<section  class="content-section full-width with-col cover rella-no-padding rella-no-margin    content-section-5b6ad4fc5fa99"><div class="row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column col-md-12"><div class="section-text text-block " ><p class="p1"><strong>Director Jeremy Bristow reports from Sierra Leone, where he is filming the Ebola outbreak on behalf of Make Productions.</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">At Heathrow I successfully crammed my bags with wipes, Dettol, sprays, bin liners and then checked them in, somehow avoiding excess baggage. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Rigorous searching of bags at the X-Ray machine. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Bought a GoPro Hero 4 Silver at Dixons … a real beauty.  There is a ‘Protune’ function that enables me to shoot in a sort of RAW mode which will give more flexibility in the edit. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Plane to Casablanca was nearly full.  Go-Pro Hero 4 is lovely in low light.  Plane full of Sierra Leonians, Indian and Lebanese businessmen.  </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Two hour delay at Casablanca. No explanation.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">A few foreigners started putting their masks on in the plane. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Arrival at Lungi Airport Freetown rather time consuming. Am going to seek permission to film there on the airside.  Straight off the plane and before entering the terminal everyone washes their hands in chlorine.  Then they fill in a personal Ebola form, go through passport control and THEN  they get a temperature gun pointed at their head and given a reading to add to their Ebola form.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Customs guys pulled me over and asked me what I was doing.  I said making a film with Medecins Sans Frontiers and they let me through.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Fairly chaotic once through into arrivals hall.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Getting on the ferry, the ferry journey and the arrival is a good and atmospheric sequence.  The sun was rising as we crossed.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Nobody touches each other, nobody shakes hands.</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">A driver and the hotel manager were there to meet me. As requested they brought two phones. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">As we turned into the drive of the hotel, a man stopped the car and pointed a thermometer gun at my head and then the driver’s and the manager’s.  I am 37.00ºC.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Made my first ebola mistake when giving the drivers petrol money – I licked my fingers to count bank notes.  They are dirty and I acquired them at the airport.  I have no mouth wash.  I sprayed my mouth with the Boots anti-viral and spat lot. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">I met another reporter working for Christian Aid. She’s been here for three weeks. She does not think the anti-viral hand foam I packed is appropriate. The reporter had a different brand. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Spent Sunday on the hotel balcony, sorting out my equipment, relaxing and talking with people who have been out in the field.  Basically, no one really knows what is really going on, whether figures are going up and down.  Medecins Sans Frontiers have figures for the people they are treating but it’s clear that there are people dying all over the country and there isn’t the capacity to deal with all of them.  Heart rending stories.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">All the best for now</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Jeremy</span></p>
</div></div></div></section>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com/director-jeremy-bristows-second-report-from-sierra-leone-where-he-is-filming-the-ebola-outbreak-on-behalf-of-make-productions/">Sierra Leone Report I</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.makeproductions.com">MAKE Productions</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
